GABRIELLE PROUST

GCProust@gmail.com 503-290.6370 linkedin.com/in/gcproust

CAREER PROFILE

Enthusiastic, ultra-organized and compassionate in harnessing chaos into efficient, orderly, working systems. Over 15 years of executive level experience with event planning, administration organization, financial management and payroll. Proficient in cutting through the red tape to accomplish goals in deadline-driven environments. Looking forward to a position that utilizes a variety of my skills and talents to help a great company serve its customers.

AREAS of EXCELLENCE

Organization and prioritization Event Planning and facilitation Presentation preparation Adapting and improving Budgeting and forecasting One-on-one training
Monitoring and reporting
Reviewing and evaluating
Accounts reconciliation
Trouble shooting

Payroll administration Contract negotiations Microsoft Office Suite Visio and Access Oracle and Quick Books

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

VP of Membership, Oregon Organizational Development Network **Secretary and Club Mentor**, District 7, Toastmasters

present present

Office Administrator

DevelopmentNow, Portland, OR

10/2010 - present

- Transformed massive chaos into orderly working systems bringing the company up to date on government requirements and strengthening written contracts.
- Improved the accounting system and found \$30,000 in missing invoices.

Executive Assistant to the Chief Financial Officer

President's Office, Oregon Health & Science University, Portland, OR

5/2005 - 9/2009

- Lead trainer in organizational systems and company protocol for several new executive assistants across different locations by request of the executive.
- Integrated monthly financial data into Board dockets and PowerPoint presentations for more productive meetings and external communications.
- Developed and monitored detailed \$3+ million budget for the Office of the President to insure meeting financial goals and expense limits.
- Served with two matrixed teams: to create more efficient computerized financial access forms and revise the travel and moving policies to strengthen adherence to company policies and procedures.
- Easily negotiated bids and contracts for services and supplies up to \$100,000 for three departments; then processed and tracked invoices on those and larger, multi-year contracts keeping them on or under budget.
- Balanced purchasing cards monthly, online and manually for CFO, President and three executive assistants which insured proper utilization of company funds.
- Effectively coordinated interdepartmental planning meetings, conference calls, contract negotiations and documents for RFPs (request for proposals) and large consulting contracts.
- Arranged logistics, prepared dockets and facilitated meetings for public and private quarterly Board meetings to insure proper protocol and public notifications.

Administrative Coordinator for both CFO and the Executive Director

Hospital Administration, Oregon Health & Science University, Portland, OR

10/2000 - 5/2005

- Project coordinator during national searches to hire additional executives and managers for Hospital Administration including: scheduling and coordinating interviews, travel arrangements, preparing reimbursements and hiring documentation resulting in smooth transitions for new employees.
- Developed comprehensive, detailed budgets for four major departments utilized by management to run the departments.
- Systemized, created databases and archived 18 years of permanent files of two previous financial executives enabling efficient search and recovery of records and saving money on storage fees.
- Provided administrative and payroll support to three major departments reporting directly to the Executive Director to maintain accurate records and government compliance standards.
- Hired, trained and supervised permanent and temporary assistants throughout departments reporting to the CFO and ED improving job skills and productivity.
- Assessed and recorded allocation of assets to correct balances for each department.
- Researched and reconciled long overdue invoices for any department in the hospital system improving accounts payable credibility and relations with vendors.
- Generated monthly accounting and customized payroll reports for eight departments, analyzed and evaluated payroll reports, identified programming errors; eliminated the expense of double payments to employees.

Office Assistant

Miller Accounting and Consulting and Edward Culp, LTC PC, Beaverton, OR

2000 tax season

- Scheduled appointments and directed inquiries for clients and assisted with administrative tasks and office procedures for effective operations.
- Produced and collated the final documents ready to submit to IRS and other government agencies.

Owner and Manager (partner)

Apartment complex in Arcata, CA

until 6/2000

- Established 100% occupancy and managed apartment building. Initiated and supervised hired labor for all repairs and contracts including \$45,000 remodeling of three units.
- Administered all accounts and maintained accurate bookkeeping systems.

Payroll Administrator

Bettendorf Trucking, Arcata, CA

2/1998 - 10/1999

- Produced and coordinated bi-weekly payroll for 230+ employees across seven divisions in two states.
- Compiled and processed new hire paperwork for efficient on-boarding of drivers across two states.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science, Physical Science, Humboldt State University. Areas of study: chemistry, physics, and geology.

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Oregon Organizational Development Network, VP Membership	5/2010 - present
Toastmaster's International, Oregon district	-
District 7 Secretary and Store Manager	2010 - 11
Club Mentor, Rising Stars, Coffee Creek Correctional Facility	2010 - present
Coordinator for Speechcraft Workshop	2009
North Coast Cooperative, Inc., Arcata, CA	
President, Board of Directors	1997 – 1999
Vice President, Board of Directors	1996 – 1997